[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Chairman Song.
Presenting, your daughter...
Hannah.
Hannah?
I'm-- I'm not here
to ask for your acceptance.
I just want to say
that the people here,
your staff...
Please rehire them.
Dynasty Hotel is okay.
Please don't close it.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
(In Korean)
That despicable woman
is not even your daughter!
What?!
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]
That despicable woman
is not your daughter!
What is she talking about?
She's a scammer, Dad!
(In Filipino) Wait, I don't
understand what you're saying.
That's not true.
[SELENA] I met her, Min-jae.
And I offered her money.
Do you really think
I want to be a Song?
There! Shove that up your bangs!
- [GASPS]
- [BRENDA] How dare you?!
You're just a cheap gold digger!
[DANIEL] I have proof, Chairman.
Hannah is your daughter.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
About the sample...
[TENSE MUSIC SWELLS]